http://www.houseboi.com/classifieds/classifieds.cgi?session_key=&print_privacy_page=on

We Highly recomend the Microsoft Internet Explorer or Firefox on our site.
Some features will not work for your browser.
We also recomend you get Version 6 if your system can run it. Python-urllib/3.8
There are currently 11 users online
Homepage> Messages> MStats > FAQ-Questions> Support> Member Benefits?>What's a Houseboi?> Classifieds > Logout
Ad #
By using Houseboi.com you are bound by the Terms of Use, Guidelines and Privacy Statement.
Browse Ads - Advanced SearchDisplay New/Updated listings from the last
60, 45, 30, 20, 14, 12, 10, 7, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1 day(s).
Houseboi.com Privacy Policy Statement
Houseboi.com is committed to safeguarding your privacy online. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of the Houseboi.com Classifieds. This policy may change from time to time so please check back periodically.
This policy will let you know:
What personally identifiable information is collected from you
What cookies are and how they are used
How your information is used
Who is collecting your information
With whom your information may be shared
What choices are available to you regarding collection, use, and distribution of your information
How you can access, update or delete your information
The kind of security precautions that are in place to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of your information
How Houseboi.com protects children's privacy
What else you should know about your online privacy
What personally identifiable information is collected from you
The Houseboi.com Classifieds collects information in several ways from different parts of our web site.
Some personal information is gathered when you register. During registration, we ask for your name and email address.
The system will also ask for your street address, city, state/province, zip/postal code, country, telephone number, and the URL of your web site, although only fields that are marked with an asterisk (*) on the registration field are required.
This information is used solely to assist you in navigating the system by automatically filling in certain forms (such as the ad posting form) with your information so that you don't have to continually re-enter it.
Once you register you are no longer anonymous to Houseboi.com - you have a username and are able to take full advantage of the many offerings of the Houseboi.com Classifieds.
In addition to registration we may ask you for personal information at other times, including (but not limited to) when you place ads or take advantage of the other features of the Houseboi.com Classifieds.
If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence.
Every page within the Houseboi.com Classifieds includes a link to this Privacy Policy.
Back to Top
What cookies are and how they are used
As part of offering and providing customizable and personalized services, the Houseboi.com Classifieds may use cookies to store and sometimes track information about you. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. Certain features of the Houseboi.com Classifieds require that you accept cookies in order to work properly. (See "What choices are available to you regarding collection, use, and distribution of your information" for more information on cookies.)
Generally, we use cookies for the following purposes:
Advertising networks that serve ads onto the Houseboi.com Classifieds may use their own cookies.
The Houseboi.com Classifieds may also collect IP addresses for system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers.
Back to Top
How your information is used
The primary goal of the Houseboi.com Classifieds in collecting personal information is to provide you, the user, with a customized experience and to assist your navigation throughout the classifieds.
Back to Top
Who is collecting your information
When you are asked for personal information on the Houseboi.com Classifieds, you are sharing that information with the Houseboi.com Classifieds alone, unless it is specifically stated otherwise.
However, some activities will, by their very nature, result in your personal information being revealed to other users of the Houseboi.com Classifieds.
For example, when you enter personal information on the ad posting form, this information will generally be included in your ad, unless specifically stated otherwise.
Back to Top
With whom your information may be shared
As a general rule, Houseboi.com will not disclose any of your personally identifiable information except when we have your permission or under special circumstances, such as when we believe in good faith that the law requires it or under the circumstances described below. Please see the Terms of Service or Use Agreements for each of our products and services for more detailed information about how your personal information may be shared.
Houseboi.com may disclose account information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating the Terms of Service of Houseboi.com or may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) the rights or property of Houseboi.com, other users of Houseboi.com, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. Houseboi.com may disclose or access account information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it and for administrative and other purposes that we deem necessary to maintain, service, and improve our products and services.
Back to Top
What choices are available to you regarding collection, use, and distribution of your information
If you choose not to register or provide personal information, you can still use most of the Houseboi.com Classifieds, but you will not be able to access areas or use features that require registration.
You also have choices with respect to cookies. By modifying your browser preferences, you have the choice to accept all cookies, to be notified when a cookie is set, or to reject all cookies. If you choose to reject all cookies you will be unable to use those services of the Houseboi.com Classifieds that require registration in order to participate.
You can still use most of the features of the Houseboi.com Classifieds even if you do not accept cookies.
Houseboi.com does not sell or rent user information to anyone. We will notify you at the time of data collection or transfer if your data will be shared with a third party and you will always have the option of not permitting the transfer. If you do not wish to allow your data to be shared, you can choose not to use a particular service.
Back to Top
How you can access, update or delete your information
We will provide you with the means to ensure that your personal information is correct and current.
You may edit or delete your user profile at any time by clicking on the "My Profile" link or graphic provided by the system once you are logged in.
Once you have logged onto the system during a given session, wherever you go on the Houseboi.com Classifieds, your information will stay with you.
If you are a previously registered user and you have lost or forgotten your password, you may obtain it by email by using our "Forgot Password" feature. Click the button on any login page to request that your password be emailed to you. We cannot provide your password by any other means.
Your Houseboi.com Classifieds account can be deleted, but doing so will result in not being able to access any of the features of the program that require user registration.
Back to Top
The kind of security precautions that are in place to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of your information
Other than the administrator of the Houseboi.com Classifieds or other authorized personnel of Houseboi.com, you are the only person who has access to your personal information.
Your user registration is password-protected to prevent unauthorized access.
We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. Houseboi.com will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited email.
Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, Houseboi.com cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online services, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems.
Back to Top
How Houseboi.com protects children's privacy
Houseboi.com is a Adult audience web site. Children should NOT access this site in any form. Houseboi.com does not share personal information about users and we do not sell or rent personal information about any of our users, regardless of age. In addition, Houseboi.com will not send any direct email offers to users who indicate they are under the age of 18.
Back to Top
What else you should know about your online privacy
Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online - for example in ads that you post or through email - that information can be collected and used by others. In short, if you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return.
Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and/or any account information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you're online.
Back to Top
Search Ads
Place Ads
Edit Ads
My Profile
My Checklist
Match Maker
Help
Homepage> MessageCenter> FAQ - Questions> Support> > > Member Benefits?>What's a Houseboi?> Classifieds
Browse Ads - Advanced Search
Proud  Member of the Free Speech Coalition
Currently Houseboi.com relies on Donations and Subscriptions!Click to become a Full Member NOW!!
Terms of Use | Privacy Statement
Content copyright © 1995-2020 Houseboi.com. All rights reserved.
Please send your questions, comments, or bug reports to the
Webmaster.
Powered by houseboi.com.Copyright © 1995-2020All rights reserved.
8:37
